ILGWU. National War Labor Board case files, 5780/085
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- War Labor Board Precedents and Procedures. (2 of 3), 1941-1945 (Box 10, Folder 2a)
- War Labor Board Precedents and Procedures. (3 of 3), 1941-1945 (Box 10, Folder 2b)
- Retroactive Pay of Workers Who Have Left Employment. (1 of 3), 1943-1944 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  Increases; Eligibility
- Retroactive Pay of Workers Who Have Left Employment. (2 of 3), 1943-1944 (Box 10, Folder 3a)
- Retroactive Pay of Workers Who Have Left Employment. (3 of 3), 1943-1944 (Box 10, Folder 3b)
- Sample Field Cases, 1943-1946 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Substandards and Vacations, Regional War Labor Policies On: (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Time Work to Piece Work - Material re: Change from, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Un-numbered Wage Stabilization Cases. (1 of 2), 1943-1945 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  Correspondence; Appeals; Cases
- Un-numbered Wage Stabilization Cases. (2 of 2), 1943-1945 (Box 10, Folder 7a)
- War Labor Disputes Act, Notices re:, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 8)